Guide to the Penn State Extension records 01131
Eberly Family Special Collections Library
- 10: Records
  - Neighborhood Youth Corporation Financial Information, undated; cuid2119; 1 Items (Box 128)
  - Neighborhood Youth Corporation Payroll, 1969-1970; cuid2120; 1 Items (Box 128)
  - Neighborhood Youth Corporation Reports, undated; cuid2121; 1 Items (Box 128)
  - News Releases, undated; cuid2122; 1 Items (Box 121)
  - Noncredit Programs in the College of Agriculture, undated; cuid2123; 1 Items (Box 178)
    Course Descriptions
  - Northeast Branch Meeting American Society of Agronomy, 1967/06; cuid2124; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Northeast Conference - Who Will Control U.S. Agriculture?, 1974/03; cuid2125; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Northeast Home Horticulture Fact Sheets #52-55, undated; cuid2126; 1 Items (Box 179)
  - Northeast Regional Center for Rural Development, undated; cuid2127; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Nutrition and the Teenager, undated; cuid2128; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Nutrition Now - EFNEP Conference, 1978/06; cuid2129; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Official File Printouts, 1972; cuid2130; 1 Items (Box 154)
  - Official Print Report, 1971; cuid2131; 1 Items (Box 150)
  - Official Printout Report, 1973; cuid2132; 1 Items (Box 150)
  - Open House - Beef Cattle and Sheep Center - Meat Animal Evaluation Center, 1967/04; cuid2133; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Oral Communication in the Office - Penn State Continuing Education, 1979/04; cuid2134; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Ornamental Horticulture Work-Experience Workshop, 1969/06; cuid2135; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Our Children Series, undated; cuid2136; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Our Product is People - College of Agriculture, undated; cuid2137; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Overview: 1986-87 Penn State University College of Agriculture, 1986-1987; cuid2138; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - PA Farm Accident Survey - Accident and Illness Report Forms, undated; cuid2139; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - PA Farm Accident Survey - Accident/Illness Reminder Sheet, undated; cuid2140; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - PA Farm Accident Survey - Brief Step-By-Step Procedure for Interviewers, undated; cuid2141; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - PA Farm Accident Survey - Interviewer's Instructions, undated; cuid2142; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - PA Farm Accident Survey - Tractor and Machinery Operator Educational Information, undated; cuid2143; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - PAFC Co-op Councils, undated; cuid2144; 1 Items; Cartographic--Maps (Box 178)
  - PAFC for Youth Leaders, undated; cuid2145; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - PA NEP/PA Tracks, 1999-2011; cuid2415 (Box 236)
  - Parenting: It's Your Job and It's Our Job, undated; cuid2146; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Parts of a Grasshopper, undated; cuid2147; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Pasto Agricultural Museum, undated; cuid2148; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - PCCEA Capital Region Letters, 2006-2009; cuid2408 (Box 235)
  - PCCEA Capital Region Minutes, 1994-2009; cuid2405 (Box 235)
  - PCCEA Capital Region Orientation Materials, 1988-1995; cuid2407 (Box 235)
  - PCCEA SE Region By-Laws and Memberships, 1998-2008; cuid2410 (Box 235)
  - PCCEA SE Region Meeting Notices, 1998-2010; cuid2409 (Box 235)
  - PCCEA State Information, 2002-2010; cuid2412 (Box 235)
  - Penalty Mail, undated; cuid2149; 1 Items; Photographic--Slides--Slide Shows (Box 162)
  - Penn State Ag Arena Benefit Sale, 1981/12; cuid2150; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Penn State College Bulletin, 1921-1947; cuid2151; 1 Items (Box 172)
  - Penn State Crops Day at Landisville, 1985, 1989; cuid2152; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Penn State Crops Day at Rock Springs, 1985/09; cuid2153; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Penn State Crops Day at Rock Springs, 1986/06; cuid2154; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Penn State Documents, undated; cuid2155; 1 Items (Box 116)
  - Penn State Farm Management Handbook, undated; cuid2156; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Penn State Publications, undated; cuid2157; 1 Items (Box 110)
  - Penn State Theatre (Spring), 1975; cuid2158; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Penn State University Boy's Forestry Training Camp, undated; cuid2159; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Penn State: The University's Continuity Commitment to Agriculture - A Special Report, undated; cuid2160; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Penn State's Annual Crops Day, 1984/06; cuid2161; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Penn State's Annual Crops Day, 1984/06; cuid2162; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pennsylvania, undated; cuid2163; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Pennsylvania Citizens' Viewpoint and Slide Show, undated; cuid2164; 1 Items; Audio--Cassette--Standard (Box 175)
  - Pennsylvania Cooperative Director School, 1983/12, 1984/01; cuid2165; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pennsylvania Cooperative Extension Service, undated; cuid2166; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Pennsylvania Council of Cooperative Extension Associations, undated; cuid2167; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Pennsylvania Crownvetch Field Days, 1971/09; cuid2168; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pennsylvania Dairy Health and Biosecurity Manual, undated; cuid2169; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Pennsylvania Economic Development Data Base System - College of Agriculture, undated; cuid2170; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pennsylvania Energy Extension Service: Providing Free Energy Conservation Assistance to Local Governments and Small Businesses, undated; cuid2171; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pennsylvania Extension: A Commitment to People, undated; cuid2172; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Pennsylvania Facts, undated; cuid2173; 1 Items (Box 177)
    Ag Info Sheet
  - Pennsylvania Farm Accident Survey Master Data Sheet, undated; cuid2174; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Pennsylvania Farm Account Book: Part II-Depreciation Schedules and Inventories, undated; cuid2175; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Pennsylvania Governor's School for Agriculture - Closing Ceremony, 1987/08; cuid2176; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pennsylvania Governor's School for Agriculture at Penn State, 1987/07/08; cuid2177; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pennsylvania Governor's School for Agriculture at Penn State, undated; cuid2178; 1 Items; Textual--Bound Volumes (Box 177)
    Yearbook
  - Pennsylvania Governor's School for the Agricultural Sciences at Penn State, 1989; cuid2179; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pennsylvania Grassland and Forage Conference, 1966/11; cuid2180; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pennsylvania Horse Racing Commission Extension Program Meeting, 1996 (Box 280)
  - Pennsylvania Livestock Day, 1977; cuid2181; 1 Items (Box 178)
    Animal Science Research Summary
  - Pennsylvania Nutrition Education Program (PA NEP) Annual Report, 2001 (Box 277)
  - Pennsylvania Nutrition Education Program (PA NEP) Annual Report, 2004 (Box 277)
  - Pennsylvania Plant Food and Protectant Educational Society Annual Meeting, 1975/01; cuid2182; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pennsylvania Poultry Federation Annual Conference Program, 1964/06; cuid2183; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pennsylvania Poultry Industry Short Courses, undated; cuid2184; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pennsylvania Publications, undated; cuid2185; 1 Items (Box 110)
  - Pennsylvania Retail Florists Conference - Future of the Industry, 1965/07; cuid2186; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pennsylvania Section Program - American Society of Agricultural Engineers, 1968/10; cuid2187; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pennsylvania Shooting Sports Program - Air Rifle, undated; cuid2188; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Pennsylvania Started Pullet Program, undated; cuid2189; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Pennsylvania State Grange Leadership School, 1966/07; cuid2190; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pennsylvania State University College of Agriculture Guidebook, undated; cuid2191; 1 Items (Box 179)
  - Pennsylvania Symposium on the Production and Utilization of the Golden Delicious Apple, 1970/08; cuid2192; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pennsylvania TVA Program - Brief Resume of Tennessee Valley Authority Program, undated; cuid2193; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Pennsylvania Vaccination Program - Protect Valuable Poultry, undated; cuid2194; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Pennsylvania Women's Agricultural Network Biannual Report, 2006-2007 (Box 277)
  - Pennsylvania Woodlands, undated; cuid2195; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Pennsylvania Youth in Action, undated; cuid2196; 1 Items (Box 178)
    4-H Community Development Guide
  - Pennsylvania's Feeder Calf Sales, 1985; cuid2197; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pennsylvania's NICE (National Institute on Cooperative Education) in 1980, cuid2198; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Penny Series, undated; cuid2199; 1 Items (Box 178)
    Ag Extension Guides
  - PENpages Information Service - Delivering Research-Based Information Directly to You!, undated; cuid2200; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - People and a Spirit, undated; cuid2201; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Personnel, undated; cuid2202; 1 Items (Box 121)
  - Personnel Management Seminar, 1975; cuid2203; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pest Control Technicians Winter Course, undated; cuid2204; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pest Management and Environmental Quality Course Examination, undated; cuid2205; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Pest Sheet Series, undated; cuid2206; 1 Items (Box 178)
    Ag Publications
  - Pesticide Safety Begins at Home, undated; cuid2207; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pilot Cooperative Oil and Gas Industrial Extension Program Final Report, 1995 (Box 280)
  - Place for You - 4-H, undated; cuid2208; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Plan and Plant, undated; cuid2209; 1 Items (Box 179)
    4-H Leader's Guide
  - Plan for Strengthening, 2000 (Box 279)
  - Plan for Strengthening Outreach and Cooperative Extension Overview and Update, 1998 (Box 280)
  - Plan of Work Update Review, 2008 (Box 278)
  - Plan of Work, 1992-1995; cuid2210; 1 Items (Box 175)
  - Plans of Work, 1988-1991; cuid2211; 1 Items (Box 176)
  - Plans of Work, 2000-2004; cuid2212; 1 Items (Box 176)
  - Plans of Work, 2000-2004 (Box 278)
  - Plans of Work Update, 1990-1991; cuid2213; 1 Items (Box 176)
  - Plans of Work Update, 2005-2006 (Box 278)
  - Plans of Work Update and Federal Report, 2003-2006 (Box 280)
  - Plant Diseases and their Management, undated; cuid2214; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Planting Plan Sketch, undated; cuid2215; 1 Items (Box 177)
    Ag and Home Economics Guide
  - Poinsettia: Programmed Disease Control Production Practice, undated; cuid2216; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Position Papers, undated; cuid2217; 1 Items (Box 121)
  - Possible Dates for Planting and Harvesting, undated; cuid2218; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Potato Culture in PA, undated; cuid2219; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Poultry Handbook, undated; cuid2220; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Poultry Products Conference, undated; cuid2221; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Poultry Products Short Course, 1966/04; cuid2222; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Poultry Science - College of Agriculture, undated; cuid2223; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Preparing Baby's Formula, undated; cuid2224; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Preparing for a Career in Nursery Management, undated; cuid2225; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Preparing for the 80s - Extension Secretarial Conference, 1981/09; cuid2226; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Preparing for the Electronic Age - Extension Secretarial Conference, 1984/10; cuid2227; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Press Releases, undated; cuid2228; 1 Items (Box 144)
  - Press Releases, undated; cuid2229; 1 Items (Box 145)
  - Preventing Harmful Residues in Gamebirds, undated; cuid2230; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Printed County Annual Reports (Duplicates), undated; cuid2231; 1 Items (Box 106)
  - Priority Educational Needs - Statewide Assessment, 1996-1999 (Box 280)
  - Professional Development, Regional, 2005-2008; cuid2435 (Box 237)
  - Professional Development, Regional, 2008-2009; cuid2436 (Box 237)
  - Professional/Technical Education Institute for Vocational Agriculture Teachers, 1983/07; cuid2232; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Profit and Financial Management, 1975/05; cuid2233; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Program Overview, 1992; cuid2234; 1 Items (Box 175)
  - Program Overview, 1992-1996 (Box 278)
  - Program Overview, 1993-1995; cuid2235; 2 Items (Box 175)
  - Program Overview, 1993-1996; cuid2236; 2 Items (Box 176)
  - Program Planning in the Land of P, undated; cuid2237; 2 Items; Photographic--Slides--Slide Shows (Box 162)
  - Program Priorities for the Cooperative Extension Service, 1983-1987 (Box 173)
  - Plan for Strengthening Outreach and Cooperative Extension, 1996 (Box 277)
  - Plan for Strengthening Outreach and Cooperative Extension Overview and Update, 1999 (Box 277)
  - Program Priority Files, 1980; cuid2238; 1 Items (Box 153)
  - Program Projections in Extension Specialties, undated; cuid2239; 1 Items (Box 117)
  - Programming for Urban Pennsylvania, undated; cuid2240; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Project Agreements, undated; cuid2241; 1 Items (Box 106)
  - Project Agreements, undated; cuid2242; 1 Items (Box 121)
  - Project Files, undated; cuid2243; 1 Items (Box 117)
  - Promoting and Advertising a Home-Based Business, undated; cuid2244; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Proposals, undated; cuid2245; 1 Items (Box 121)
  - Proposed Management Education Curriculum for CEDs, 1990; cuid2246; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Pruning Apple Trees, undated; cuid2247; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - PSEC Penn State Extension Council, 2011; cuid2411 (Box 235)
  - Public Affairs Leadership Program, undated; cuid2248; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Public Health Entomology Ag Publications, undated; cuid2249; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Public Relations Committee, undated; cuid2250; 1 Items (Box 117)
  - Publications, undated; cuid2251; 1 Items (Box 121)
  - Publications and Reports, undated; cuid2252; 1 Items (Box 117)
  - Publications of the Pennsylvania State University College of Agriculture, undated; cuid2253; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Purebred Breeders Short Course, 1962/03; cuid2254; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Quick Look at Pennsylvania Groundwater, undated; cuid2255; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Reach for a New Horizon - Nutrition Aide Conference, 1976/06; cuid2256; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Recipes (Lunch, Breakfast, Snacks), undated; cuid2257; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Regional Extension Fruit School: From the Nursery to the Grower, 1986/10; cuid2258; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Regional Program Team Agriculture, 1999-2010; cuid2420 (Box 236)
  - Regional Program Team Urban Agriculture, 2003-2012; cuid2418 (Box 236)
  - Regional Staff Assistants Conference, Fall, 1999-2005; cuid2423 (Box 236)
  - Regulations, 1961, 1970; cuid2259; 1 Items (Box 172)
  - Report of Task Force on Ext. Organization, undated; cuid2260; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Report of Task Force on Extension Organization, 1972; cuid2261; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Reporting Forms, 1968; cuid2262; 1 Items (Box 149)
  - Reports, 1967; cuid2263; 1 Items (Box 150)
  - Reports, undated; cuid2264; 1 Items (Box 110)
  - Reports and Documents, undated; cuid2265; 1 Items (Box 144)
  - Reproductive Physiology of the Male: Present Status and Future Prospects - A Symposium in Honor of John O. Almquist, 1982/06; cuid2266; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Request for Optional Forage Tests, 1978/06; cuid2267; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Request for Optional Soil Tests, 1977/01; cuid2268; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Rough Mill Lumber Workshop, 1975; cuid2269; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Rural Real Estate Appraisers Workshop, 1967/05; cuid2270; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Rural Sociology Annual Report, 1961; cuid2271; 1 Items (Box 124)
  - Safe and Responsible Hunting, undated; cuid2272; 1 Items (Box 178)
    Correspondence Courses in Agriculture
  - Sales Tax correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 280)
  - Salmonellae in Foods Conference, 1968/03; cuid2273; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Scientific Developments in Agriculture Open House, 1964/04; cuid2274; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Scorecard, 2001 (Box 280)
  - SE CED Retreat, 2004-2005; cuid2437 (Box 237)
  - SE Leadership Team Meetings: Adobe Connect, 2008; cuid2448 (Box 240)
  - SE Leadership Team Meeting - Adobe Connect, 2009; cuid2454 (Box 240)
  - SE CED Leadership Team Meeting - Adobe Connect, 2010; cuid2455 (Box 240)
  - SE CED Leadership Team Meeting - Adobe Connect, 2011; cuid2456 (Box 240)
  - SE Leadership Team Meetings: Berks and Lehigh Counties, 2008; cuid2446 (Box 239)
  - SE Leadership Team Meetings: Berks and Montgomery Counties, 2008; cuid2450 (Box 240)
  - SE Leadership Team Meetings: Berks County, 2009; cuid2453 (Box 240)
  - SE Leadership Team Meetings: Berks County and USDA Presentations, 2008; cuid2451 (Box 240)
  - SE Leadership Team Meeting: Chester County, 2009; cuid2452 (Box 240)
  - SE Leadership Team Meetings: Lehigh, Bucks and Philadelphia Counties, 2007; cuid2444 (Box 239)
  - SE Leadership Team Meetings: Philadelphia and Berks Counties, 2008; cuid2447 (Box 239)
  - SE Outreach Conference, 2001-2004; cuid2428 (Box 237)
  - SE Outreach Conference, 2003-2006; cuid2431 (Box 237)
  - SE Region Conference, 2002-2006; cuid2432 (Box 237)
  - SE Region Extension Board Visits, 2004-2005; cuid2406 (Box 235)
  - SE Region Staffing, 2005-2006; cuid2457 (Box 240)
  - SE Region Strategic Plan, 2004-2009; cuid2438 (Box 237)
  - SE Regional Staff Conference, 2010; cuid2424 (Box 236)
  - Seminar Programs and Booklets, undated; cuid2275; 1 Items (Box 116)
  - Sewage Sludge and Diagnostic Soil Tests - Information and Fee Schedule, 1987/07; cuid2276; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Sheep Breeding and Production Conference, 1982/11; cuid2277; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Short Courses in Meat Science and Technology, undated; cuid2278; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Sixtieth Anniversary Celebration of the School of Forest Resources, 1967; cuid2279; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Skills for Working Together, undated; cuid2280; 1 Items (Box 177)
    Cooperative Extension Guide
  - Small Fruit and Tree Fruit Field Day, 1986/09/16; cuid2281; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Small Scale Agriculture at Penn State: Growing Bulb Crops in the Home Garden (Onions, Leeks, and Garlic), undated; cuid2282; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Sod Selection and Installation, undated; cuid2283; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Soil Testing and Your Lawn, undated; cuid2284; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Some Facts About Agriculture Education and Home Economics Extension Service, undated; cuid2285; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Some Significant Dates, undated; cuid2286; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Specialist Plans of Work, 1920-1929; cuid2287; 1 Items (Box 110)
  - Specialist Time Distribution, 1925-1955; cuid2288; 1 Items (Box 152)
  - Spirit of the 70's, undated; cuid2289; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Spray Schedules for Fruits and Vegetables, undated; cuid2290; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Spring and Summer Insect Control on Hay Crops, 1965/02; cuid2291; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Sprinkler Irrigation Conference, 1967/04; cuid2292; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Staff Assistants Conference, 1999-2004; cuid2422 (Box 236)
  - Staff Assistants Conference, 2005-2006; cuid2421 (Box 236)
  - Staff Conference - Agricultural and Home Economics Extension Service, 1967/12; cuid2293; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Staff Conferences, undated; cuid2294; 1 Items (Box 142)
  - Staffing Plan, 2001-2002; cuid2425 (Box 236)
  - Staffing Plan, 2002-2005; cuid2458 (Box 240)
  - Standardbred Conference, 1970/07; cuid2295; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Staphylococci in Foods Conference, 1973/03; cuid2296; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - State FFA Activities Week, 1967-1968/06; cuid2297; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - State Plans of Work, 1988-1997 (Box 279)
  - State Plans of Work and Annual Action Plans, 1996-1999; cuid2299; 1 Items (Box 175)
  - State Plan of Work Annual Update, 1993 (Box 279)
  - State Plan of Work Annual Report, 1992 (Box 280)
  - State Plan of Work Annual Report, 1994 (Box 280)
  - State Plans of Work for Pennsylvania, 1987/06; cuid2300; 1 Items (Box 176)
  - State Plans of Work for Pennsylvania, 1988/04; cuid2301; 1 Items (Box 176)
  - State Plans of Work for Pennsylvania, 1988/07; cuid2302; 1 Items (Box 176)
  - State Plan of Work for Pennsylvania, 1991/08; cuid2298; 1 Items (Box 176)
  - State Plan of Work for Pennsylvania, Final, 1992-1995 (Box 280)
  - Statement of Extension Service in Agriculture and Home Economics, 1954; cuid2303; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Statewide Program Catalog, 2010-2011 (Box 277)
  - Statewide Survey of Air Pollution Damage to Vegetation, undated; cuid2304; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Statistical Reporting Data Processing Information, undated; cuid2305; 1 Items (Box 110)
  - Statistical Reports, undated; cuid2306; 1 Items (Box 153)
  - Statistical Reports and A100s Binder, 1962-1973; cuid2307; 1 Items (Box 153)
  - Statistical Reports and Printouts, 1966; cuid2308; 1 Items (Box 154)
  - Statistical Reports and Printouts, 1968; cuid2309; 1 Items (Box 154)
  - Statistical Reports and Printouts, 1975-1976; cuid2310; 1 Items (Box 149)
  - Statistical Reports and Printouts, 1977-1978; cuid2311; 2 Items (Box 151)
  - Statistical Reports Bound Volume and A100s, 1925-1973; cuid2312; 1 Items (Box 152)
  - Statistical Reports Plan of Work Printouts, 1967-1969; cuid2313; 1 Items (Box 147)
  - Statistical Reports Plan of Work Printouts, 1970-1976; cuid2314; 1 Items (Box 146)
  - Statistical Reports Plan of Work Printouts, 1977-1978; cuid2315; 1 Items (Box 147)
  - Stored Grain Pests Series, undated; cuid2316; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Strategic Plan Update, 1997-2005 (Box 280)
  - Strategic Planning - Various Documents, 1997-2004; cuid2439 (Box 237)
  - Suggested Feeding Programs for Small Poultry Flocks - Egg Laying Chickens, undated; cuid2317; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Sulfa Residue Problems in Calves Slaughtered in PA, undated; cuid2318; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Summary of Activities Bound Volume, 1922-1932; cuid2319; 1 Items (Box 153)
  - Summary of Activities Bound Volume, 1946-1966; cuid2320; 2 Items (Box 153)
  - Summary of Agriculture Extension Accomplishments, 1948; cuid2321; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Summer Work Conference - 76 and Beyond, 1976/07; cuid2322; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Supplemental Accident Report Form, undated; cuid2323; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Supplemental Illness Report Form, undated; cuid2324; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Supplementary Reports, undated; cuid2325; 1 Items (Box 108)
  - Survey of Engineering Graduates, undated; cuid2326; 1 Items (Box 172)
  - Swine Diseases Program, 1977/03; cuid2327; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Symposium on Egg Shell Damage, 1969/05; cuid2328; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Symposium on Environmental Quality, Foods, and Nutrition, 1970/05; cuid2329; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Symposium on Protection of the Environment and Food Base, 1971/05; cuid2330; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - System Software Manual, undated; cuid2331; 1 Items (Box 145)
  - Systems Approach to Dairy Extension Programs, 2001 (Box 280)
  - Task Narratives, 1976; cuid2332; 1 Items (Box 125)
  - Task Narratives #1-74, 1976; cuid2333; 1 Items (Box 129)
  - Task Narratives #1-98, 1972; cuid2334; 1 Items (Box 126)